http://uppercredit.com/privacy-policy

Privacy policy - Upper Credit Humane Society
Skip to Content
Featured animal:
Mia »
Search for:
Privacy policy
The Upper Credit Humane Society is committed to protecting personal information for all our donors, supporters, volunteers, adoptive families, employees and board members.
Collecting personal information
The UCHS collects and uses personal information for the following purposes:
Verify your identity
Comply with federal, provincial, local law and by-law requirements
Comply with tax requirements
Send out communication
Announce or register for UCHS events
Request donations
Sharing information
The UCHS does not sell or share personal information or contact lists with other non-profit organizations, agencies or third parties.
Maintaining personal information
Security systems are in place to protect personal information whether it is in an electronic or paper-based format.
Disposal of personal information
The UCHS will retain personal information for as long as is required to effectively provide services and answer any questions about services provided, and for our own legal accountability and accountability to external regulatory bodies.
The UCHS shall use care and caution when disposing of personal information. Paper files containing personal information will be shredded. Electronic information will be deleted and, when hardware is discarded, the hard drive will be physically destroyed.
Instagram
Facebook
Twitter
Accessibility | Privacy Policy | Members
©2020 Upper Credit Humane Society. Website by floating-point
